<resources>
    <string name="app_name">3GStore</string>
    <string name="nomeAppSpashPage">3G STORE</string>
    <string name="email">E-Mail</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Name Surname</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Points: </string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Shopping Cart</string>
    <string name="menu_promozioni">Promotions</string>
    <string name="menu_marangicoin">Your MarangiCoin</string>
    <string name="menu_contatti">Yours contacts</string>
    <string name="menu_quit">Quit</string>
    <string name="menu_gioco">Quizcoin</string>
    <string name="menu_informazioni">Products Info</string>
    <string name="new_game_label">Insert Coin</string>
    <string name="killscreen_label">Kill Screen</string>
    <string name="exit_label">Exit</string>
    <string name="cronologia">Order History</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="badge_qty"></string>


    <!-- Login e Registrazione -->
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="back_login">Already registered? Login!</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed, check your email and password or sign up</string>
    <string name="minimum_password">Password too short, enter minimum 6 characters!</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="lbl_forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_msg">Insert your registered Email for receive password reset instrucion</string>
    <string name="btn_reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="btn_back">Back</string>
    <string name="product_unavailable">The scanned product is unavailable</string>
    <string name="lista_vuota">Your shopping cart is empty</string>
    <string name="shopping_amount">Total Amount: </string>
    <string name="firstName">First name</string>
    <string name="secondName">Second name</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter email address!</string>
    <string name="enter_psw">Enter password!</string>
    <string name="reset_email_success">We have sent you instructions to reset your password!</string>
    <string name="reset_email_fail">Failed to send reset email!</string>
    <string name="registration_fail">Registration failed!</string>

    <!-- MarangiCoin -->
    <string name="your_marangiCoin">Current MarangiCoin: </string>
    <string name="exchange_marangiCoin">Every 20 MarangiCoin you get 1€ of discount on any of our products</string>
    <string name="exchange_button">Exchange</string>
    <string name="marangiCoin">MarangiCoin symbol</string>
    <string name="marangiCoin_exchange">MarangiCoin to exchange</string>
    <string name="euro_exchange">Euro you get</string>
    <string name="current_discount">Current discount: €</string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="profile_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="email_summary">Change your Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="password_vecchia">Old Password</string>
    <string name="password_nuova">New Password</string>
    <string name="password_summary">Change your Password</string>
    <string name="cards">Cards</string>
    <string name="card1">**** **** **** 1234</string>
    <string name="card2">**** **** **** 5678</string>
    <string name="addCard">Add Card</string>
    <string name="cardNum">Card Number</string>
    <string name="tos">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="cards_summary">Manage your payment cards</string>
    <string name="touchid">Touch ID</string>
    <string name="touchid_summary">Enable/Disable Touch ID</string>
    <string name="offers">Offers Notification</string>
    <string name="offers_summary">Enable/Disable notifications for offers on products near you</string>
    <string name="elimina_prodotto_successo">Product removed successfully</string>
    <string name="carrello_vuoto">Your shopping cart is empty!</string>
    <string name="saldo_insufficente_nosconto">The selected payment credit is insufficient</string>
    <string name="saldo_insufficente_sisconto">The selected payment credit and your discount amount are insufficient</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>

    <!-- Toast Settings-->
    <string name="camps">Compile all camps</string>
    <string name="psw_short">The password is too short! Insert at least 6 characters</string>
    <string name="psw_not_equal">The two passwords don\'t match</string>
    <string name="psw_change_failed">Password change failed</string>
    <string name="psw_change_success">Password succesfully changed!</string>
    <string name="auth_error_psw">Authentication error, maybe your password is wrong</string>
    <!-- mail-->
    <string name="email_change_failed">Email change failed!</string>
    <string name="email_change_success">Email succesfully changed!</string>
    <string name="auth_error_mail">Authentication error, maybe your email/password is wrong</string>
    <string name="wrong_psw">Wrong password</string>

    <!-- Acquisto fragment -->
    <string name="info_intestazione">Purchase Informations</string>
    <string name="info_totale_articoli">Summary order:</string>
    <string name="info_punti_guagnati">MarangiCoin earned:</string>
    <string name="impo_intestazione">Payment Settings</string>
    <string name="impo_carta_addebitata">Balance available:</string>
    <string name="impo_sconto_disponibile">Discount available:</string>
    <string name="impo_checkbox_sconto">Do you want to use your discount?</string>
    <string name="finale_intestazione">Confirm order</string>
    <string name="finale_totale_ordine">Total amount:</string>
    <string name="finale_bottone_acquista">Buy now!</string>
    <string name="on">Yes</string>
    <string name="off">No</string>
    <string name="finale_sconto_rimasto">Remaining discount:</string>
    <string name="acquisto_riuscito">Purchase successful!</string>


    <!-- Fragment cambio password -->
    <string name="example_text1">Change Password Fragment</string>

    <!-- Cronologia Ordini -->
    <string name="ordini">Your order: </string>


    <!-- Tutorial -->
    <string name="titolo_1">Scansiona il codice del prodotto</string>
    <string name="titolo_2">Aggiungi al tuo carrello</string>
    <string name="titolo_3">Paga in completa tranquillità</string>

    <string name="descrizione_1">Clicca sul pulsante per aprire la fotocamera</string>
    <string name="descrizione_2">Clicca sul pulsante per aggiungere il prodotto al carrello</string>
    <string name="descrizione_3">Clicca sul pulsante del carrello per pagare</string>


    <string name="cambia">Change Password</string>
    <string name="new_email">New E-mail</string>
    <string name="cambia_email">Change E-mail</string>


    <string name="termini_di_servizio">

        General Conditions of Use and Sale
GENERAL CONDITIONS OF USE
Please read these general conditions of use ("General Terms of Use") carefully before using the 3G Store Services. By using the 3G Store Services, you fully accept these General Terms and Conditions of Use. The 3G Store Software (APP) was granted for use by 4uem spa, based in via Genova 208, Turin VAT: 10961410015, which manages all rights until 31-12 2020. In this document the General Conditions of use of the 3G Store service and all sites owned or used by 4uem spa which have exclusive use rights, which are redirected to the mobilefunnel website, are reported. it (hereinafter referred to as the "General Conditions" and the "Site" respectively) to which anyone intends to navigate on the pages of the same must abide by. Access to the APP or the Site and any action that involves browsing its web pages constitute acceptance of the General Conditions. In the event that the user does not intend to accept the General Conditions, it is sufficient for him to refrain from browsing the pages of the Site and not register with the 3G Store APP. Anyone accessing the Website or the 3G Store APP implicitly declares not to use the Site and the material contained therein for illicit purposes or in any case contrary to the laws in force. The General Terms and Conditions may be modified by 4uem spa at any time, without prior notice being given to users and without prejudice to the latter\'s responsibility to view them periodically before accessing the contents of the Site. Access to the Site or to the Website APP after these changes implies full and unconditional adherence to the General Conditions as amended. If inside the web pages of the Site or the APP are offered goods and services or presented contents subject to specific terms and conditions reported in these pages, the same shall prevail over these General Conditions.

Defined roles:
Manager: 4uem spa
Administrator: an affiliated company that has access both to the Admin control panel
User: customer who registers via email for free to the 3G Store service

1 Service activation
To become affiliated the company must accept in advance these general terms and conditions and the privacy policy to pay the balance or the first installment and activation by bank transfer or other agreed form. Only after having paid the entire agreed sum or the agreed installments will the manager activate the affiliate service. The operator has the full faculty to stop the service immediately, without giving any written communication to the service at the moment in which the affiliate does not respect the contractual conditions, the privacy legislation and point 1.

2 ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS
When you use 3G Store Services or send us e-mails, text messages (SMS) and other communications from your computer or mobile device, communicate with us electronically. We will be able to communicate with you in various ways, for example by e-mail, text messages (SMS), in-app notifications, or by posting messages and communications on the site or through other 3G Store Services, such as our Communications Center. Without prejudice to the specific mandatory legal provisions, for the purposes of this contract, you agree to receive electronic communications from us and acknowledge that all contracts, notifications, information and other communications we provide to you electronically satisfy the requirement of written form, when required by law.

3 COPYRIGHT AND DATA RIGHTS
All contents present or made available through the 3G Store Services in the form of texts, graphics, logos, icon buttons, images, audio files, digital downloads, data collections and software are the property of 3G Store or its suppliers. content and are protected by Italian laws and international laws on copyright and
database rights. The list of all the contents present or made available through the 3G Store Services is the exclusive property of 3G Store and is protected by Italian laws and international laws on copyright and database rights.
It is not permitted to systematically extract and / or reuse parts of the 3G Store Services without the express written consent of 3G Store. In particular, it is not allowed to use data mining, robots or similar acquisition or extraction devices to extract (one or more times) to reuse any substantial part of any 3G Store Services, without our express written consent. You may not even create and / or publish your own database that reproduces substantial parts (eg prices and product lists) of the 3G Store Services without the express written consent of 3G Store.
3 MARKS
The graphic material, the logos, the page headers, the icon buttons, the characters and the service marks included or made available through any of the 3G Store Services are trademarks or distinctive signs of 3G Store. The brands and the distinctive signs of 3G Store cannot be used in relation to products or services other than 3G Store, in such a way as to generate confusion among the customers or in any way that could denigrate or discredit 3G Store. All other trademarks not owned by 3G Store that appear on any of the 3G Store Services are the property of their respective owners, which may or may not be connected, connected to 3G Store or sponsored by 3G Store.

4 PATENTS
The 3G Store Services and the functionalities accessible through these services are protected by one or more patents owned by 3G Store. The 3G Store Services use in whole or in part one or more patents based on licenses.

5 LICENSE FOR ACCESS TO 3G Store SERVICES
Provided that you comply with these General Terms and Conditions of Use, the Terms of Service, and that you pay any applicable fees, 4uem spa or its content provider will grant you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable and non-exclusive license sublicensable for access to 3G Store Services and for personal and / or commercial use. It is not possible to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell, visit or in any other way use the 3G Store Services in whole or in part without our express written consent for any commercial use. It is not possible to proceed with framing or use framing techniques to unduly appropriate any trademark, logo or other proprietary information (including images, text, page settings, or format) of 3G Store without our express written consent. You may not use any meta tags or any other "hidden text" using the 3G Store name or trademarks without our express written consent. You must not misuse the 3G Store Services. You can use the 3G Store Services only within the limits set by law. Violation of these General Terms and Conditions of Use or Terms of Service will result in the revocation of the authorization or license issued by 4uem spa.

6 YOUR ACCOUNT
If you use the 3G Store Services, you are required to keep your account and your password confidential and to control access to your computer and your devices, and you agree, within the limits allowed by the applicable legal provisions, to be held responsible for all the activities that will be carried out with your account and your password. You agree to take all necessary precautions to ensure that your password remains secure and confidential and you commit yourself to inform us immediately if you have reason to believe that any third party is aware of your password, or if your password either, or presumably is going to be, used in an unauthorized manner. You are responsible for ensuring that the data you provide to us is correct and complete and to notify us immediately of any change in the
and information you provided. You will be able to access and update most of the information provided in the WIEV PROFILE section of the site. You will not have to use the 3G Store Services: (i) in such a way as to cause, or to be able to cause, interruptions, damage or malfunctions to the 3G Store Services and its functions, or (ii) for fraudulent purposes, or otherwise to commit illegal activities , or (iii) to cause disturbance, prejudice or apprehension.

4uem spa reserves the right to prevent access to the site and / or 3G Store Services, to suspend or terminate an account, to remove or modify the contents of the site at our discretion, in the event of violation of the applicable legal provisions , of these General Terms and Conditions of Use or of the applicable guidelines or policies.

7 REVIEWS, COMMENTS, COMMUNICATIONS AND OTHER CONTENTS
It is permitted to publish reviews, comments and other content, send electronic postcards and other communications and submit suggestions, ideas, comments, questions or other information, as long as the content is not illicit (or obscene, abusive, intimidating, defamatory, does not violate privacy , intellectual property rights or is not otherwise offensive to 3G Store and / or third parties or regrettable and is not or at least does not contain viruses, political propaganda, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass e-mails or whatever other form of spamming). You will not be able to use a false e-mail address, pretend to be another person or subject or otherwise lie about the origin of a postcard or other content. We reserve the right (but we have no obligation to act in the absence of a complete notification form in its entirety) to remove

    </string>

</resources>
